<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE manifesto SYSTEM "manifesto.dtd">
<manifesto>
    <meta>
        <titulo>TPC 5</titulo>
        <subtitulo>Página Web em formato single page app, de uma toDo list, utilizando framework express</subtitulo>
        <data>2023-03-01</data>
        <autor>
            <nome>Gonçalo Braz Afonso</nome>
            <id>a93178</id>
            <gitlink>https://github.com/brazafonso/RPCW2023</gitlink>
        </autor>
        <uc>Representação e Processamento de Conhecimento na Web(RPCW)</uc>
    </meta>
    <resumo>
        <p>Create a Single Page Application (SPA) for toDo lists;</p>
        <p>Main page should have 3 areas: insert form, toDo task list and resolved task list;</p>
        <p>Task model is composed by: dateDued (deadline); who (who is supposed to do it) and what (task description);</p>
        <p>Add edit and delete operations to both lists;</p>
        <p>To implement edit and delete study howto make PUT and DELETE requests to json-server;</p>
        <p>When a task is submitted through the form, it will appear in toDO list;</p>
        <p>Add a button to each task in toDo list to change the status to solved (task should move form one list to the other);</p>
        <p>Possible extras: maintain lists of task types, task descriptions, ..., that are preloaded into select components... make a nice interface, even responsive.</p>
    </resumo>
    <resultados>
        <resultado path="routes/index.js" identificador="index">Script <i>JavaScript</i> do servidor para tratar requests.</resultado>
        <resultado path="controllers/tasks.js" identificador="tasks_api">Script <i>JavaScript</i> com funções para obter dados do dataset do json-server.</resultado>
        <resultado path="views" identificador="views">Conjunto das páginas web em formato <i>pug</i>.</resultado>
        <resultado path="tasks.json" identificador="tasks">Json/dataset com as tasks. Modificado pelo servidor em tempo real.</resultado>
    </resultados>
</manifesto>